https://www.121directmail.co.uk/121-direct-mail-privacy-policy/

CLOSE
This privacy policy sets out how 121 Direct Mail uses and protects any data that you provide us with when using our services, this website or visiting our offices.
We are keen to ensure that your privacy is protected. Any data requested by which you can be identified when using this website will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. This Privacy Policy may be updated to ensure that we adhere to current legislation and best practice.
Firstly, we are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have initiated appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online and at our offices and warehouse.
How do 121 Direct Mail Limited use your data?
Our Clients
We provide a range of professional services, some of which require us to process personal data in order to fulfil our contractual agreements.
Where we need to process personal data to provide these services, we ask our clients to provide the necessary information to the data subjects regarding its use.
Occasionally, for certain services, clients or activities, we may process special categories of personal data.
We also collect personal data from our clients when providing services to them under the legal grounds of consent or legitimate interest & contractual use.
Visitors to the 121 Direct Mail Premises
CCTV
CCTV is in operation at our premises. The images captured are securely stored and only accessed on a ‘Senior Director Only Viewing Policy’ basis (i.e. to look into an incident). We use the CCTV images for the legitimate purposes of promoting security and safety of our personnel and members of the public as well as preventing and detecting crime. We may disclose CCTV images to law enforcement bodies as requested and permitted by data protection law.
CCTV recording are generally automatically overwritten after a period of time (approximately 14 days after being recorded) unless an issue is identified that requires investigation where images are saved.
Wi-Fi
Our guest WIFI network is not monitored for any usage purposes. We cannot inspect any encrypted web pages and therefore do not have access to any information (personal or otherwise) that the user might share via these pages whilst on our guest Wi-Fi system.
Staff and Contractors
We collect personal data concerning our own staff and contractors as part of the administration, management of business activities. More information about how we handle this information can be found by referring to our Privacy Procedure document.
This data is processed under the legal grounds of Contract, Consent & Legal Obligation.
Use by 121 Direct Mail Limited
Administering, managing and developing our business services
We may process personal data in order to run our business, including:
managing our relationship with clients and potential clients;
developing our business and services (such as identifying client needs and improvements to our products & services)
maintaining and operating our IT systems
administering and managing our website
Security, quality and risk management
We have a broad range of security measures in place to protect data subject’s information and personal data.
We continually monitor the services we provide our clients for quality purposes. This may involve processing personal data stored on the relevant client file. We have policies and procedures to monitor our services and manage risks in relation to the client work we undertake.
Providing our clients (and potential clients) with information about us and our range of service
Unless we are asked not to, we use client and prospective client business contact details to provide information that we think will be of interest about us and our services. For example, industry updates and marketing collateral, as well as other services that may be relevant.
This data is processed for the purpose of the legitimate interests by us to promote our business and services.
Retention of Data
We will only retain your information as long as is necessary to carry out the purposes for which it was provided or meet a particular obligation. (Please refer to the GDPR 121 Client Checklist)
Personal data may be held for longer periods where extended retention periods are required by law or regulation
Personal Information Regulator Options
When asked to provide personal information on https://www.121directmail.co.uk look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by any 3rd party for direct marketing purposes, 121 Direct Mail do not sell any of their client data or information.
If you have previously agreed to using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us info@121directmail.co.uk . We will not sell (apart from as a part of sale of the assets of 121 Direct Mail), distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law.
You may request details of personal information which we hold under GDPR legislation, however, a small processing fee of £10 will be payable.
If you would like a copy of the information held on you, please write to:
The GDPR Officer, 121 Direct Mail
Charter House, Latham Close
Bredbury Park Industrial Estate
Stockport SK6 2SD
If you believe that any data we are holding is incorrect or incomplete, please contact us as soon as possible. You can contact us at the above email address or email. info@121directmail.co.uk
Mailings
Home
About us
Direct Mail Services
Data Division
Quality Assurance
Useful Info
Contact
What Makes Direct Mail Work
0845 4000 121 info@121directmail.co.uK121 Direct Mail, Charter House, Latham Close, Bredbury Park Industrial Estate, Bredbury, STOCKPORT, Cheshire, SK6 2SDMailings
Home
About us
Direct Mail Services
Data Division
Quality Assurance
Useful Info
Contact
Newsflash
What Makes Direct Mail Work
0845 4000 121 info@121directmail.co.uK121 Direct Mail, Charter House, Latham Close, Bredbury Park Industrial Estate, Bredbury, STOCKPORT, Cheshire, SK6 2SDCopyright 2020  ~  121 Direct Mail Ltd  ~  Company Registration No 05532478  ~  ICO Registration No Z9273334 ~ Sitemap ~ Articles
Copyright 2020  ~  121 Direct Mail Ltd  ~  Company Registration No 05532478  ~  ICO Registration No Z9273334 ~ Sitemap ~ Articles
